- Why do you need this...?
- No, no, no.
(Alex:)- Sorry.
- I am glad you asked.
(Sheldon:)- Oh.
- Are you familiar with the Higgs boson?
Heh. Of course.
(Penny:)It is... It's been in the news.
And it's a very famous boson.
Nice try. No, in 1964...
(Sheldon:)...Dr. Peter Higgs, accomplished
self-promoter and physicist...
(Sheldon:)...he wrote a paper
postulating the existence...
(Sheldon:)...of a subatomic particle
called the Higgs boson.
(Sheldon:)Now, initially, the paper was rejected.
(Sheldon:)But recently, he was proven right.
(Sheldon:)And now he's on the fast track
to win a Nobel Prize.
- Yeah. That's basically what I said.
- Yeah...
(Sheldon:)The point is, Higgs is being celebrated
for work he did 50 years ago.
(Sheldon:)So that got me thinking.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I've already hit upon the idea
that will win me my Nobel Prize.
(Leonard:)I didn't know they gave Nobel Prizes
for making boom-boom in the potty.
(Penny:)You really think there's some kind of
scientific discovery in here?